export const quiz = [
  {
    topic: "cs",
    totalQuestions: 5,
    questions: [
      {
        question:
          "Which function is used to serialize an object into a JSON string in Javascript?",
        choices: ["stringify()", "parse()", "convert()", "None of the above"],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: 0,
      },
      {
        question:
          "Which of the following keywords is used to define a variable in Javascript?",
        choices: ["var", "let", "var and let", "None of the above"],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: 2,
      },
      {
        question:
          "Which of the following methods can be used to display data in some form using Javascript?",
        choices: [
          "document.write()",
          "console.log()",
          "window.alert",
          "All of the above",
        ],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: 3,
      },
      {
        question: "How can a datatype be declared to be a constant type?",
        choices: ["const", "var", "let", "constant"],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: 0,
      },
      {
        question:
          "Which of the following keywords is used to define a variable in Javascript?",
        choices: ["var", "let", "var and let", "None of the above"],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: 2,
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    topic: "math",
    totalQuestions: 5,
    questions: [
      {
        question:
          "2+3=",
        choices: ["34", "23", "5", "None of the above"],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: 2,
      },
      {
        question:
          "Which of the following keywords is used to define a variable in Javascript?",
        choices: ["var", "let", "var and let", "None of the above"],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: 2,
      },
      {
        question:
          "Which of the following methods can be used to display data in some form using Javascript?",
        choices: [
          "document.write()",
          "console.log()",
          "window.alert",
          "All of the above",
        ],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: 3,
      },
      {
        question: "How can a datatype be declared to be a constant type?",
        choices: ["const", "var", "let", "constant"],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: 0,
      },
      {
        question:
          "Which of the following keywords is used to define a variable in Javascript?",
        choices: ["var", "let", "var and let", "None of the above"],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: 2,
      },
    ],
  },
];
